// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Father of Mathematics",
    answer: "Archimedes",
    options: [
      "Archimedes",
      "Euclid",
      "Carl Friedrich Gauss ",
      "René Descartes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If the initial side is overlapping on the terminal side, then angle is ________",
    answer: "0°",
    options: [
      "360°",
      "90°",
      "0°",
      "180°"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 1 radian is?",
    answer: "57°16’",
    options: [
      "54°48’",
      "57°16’",
      "180°",
      "17°46’"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "For principle of mathematical induction to be true, what type of number should ‘n’ be?",
    answer: "Whole number",
    options: [
      "Natural number",
      "Rational number",
      "Any form of number",
      "Whole number"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: ". By principle of mathematical induction, 24n-1 is divisible by which of the following?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "5",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " P(n) = n(n2 – 1). Which of the following does not divide P(k+1)?",
    answer: "k+3",
    options: [
      "k+3",
      "k",
      "k+5",
      "k+2"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " n3 + 5n is divisible by which of the following?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "5",
      "11",
      "15",
      "3"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The point (4, 0, 0) lie on _____________",
    answer: "X-axis",
    options: [
      "X-axis",
      "Y-axis",
      "Z-axis",
      "Y-Z plane"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " Find the distance of point (2, 3, 5) from X-Y plane.",
    answer: "5 units",
    options: [
      "6 units",
      "2 units",
      "4 units",
      "5 units"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 3-D geometry has ______________ octants.",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "1",
      "8",
      "7",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  
];